<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[5sky engineer]]></title>
  <link href="http://nobita-isc.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://nobita-isc.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2015-04-30T16:54:17+07:00</updated>
  <id>http://nobita-isc.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Vu Xuan Duong]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015/04/30 Diary of an Android programmer]]></title>
    <link href="http://nobita-isc.github.io/blog/2015/04/30/diary-of-an-android-programmer/"/>
    <updated>2015-04-30T00:00:00+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://nobita-isc.github.io/blog/2015/04/30/diary-of-an-android-programmer</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2>30-Apr-2015</h2>

<p>Yesterday, I started learning Android programming from scatch after a long
thought. Why a long thought? To make a long story short, I have NOT coded any
thing for the last 3 years, now I decided to coding and making some interesting
stuffs by my own.</p>

<p>It seems to be not easy as it looks because technology &amp; new android version is
changing/releasing in a shorter period of time, and catching up with that
requires greate effort &amp; time, but on the other hand, I am stucking in current
boring job (which I really don’t see my passion in it).</p>

<p>Time to change. I suppose. Even if I am out of date, it is time to catch up with
new tech &amp; fun, time to see &amp; meet more friend. I need to be a stronger
personality, now, no more delay to any specific time in the future anymore.
Current job does not feed my soul, my curiousity or my passion.</p>

<p>Time to change, time to chase my dream</p>

<p>OK, just start, with some questions still I have no answer below:</p>

<ol>
<li><strong>Why Android studio(IDE) says that ActionBarActivity is deprecated ?</strong></li>
</ol>


<p>Answer:</p>

<p>….Coming soon&hellip;</p>

<p>Cheers,</p>

<p>nobita-isc</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hello World]]></title>
    <link href="http://nobita-isc.github.io/blog/2013/05/12/hello-world/"/>
    <updated>2013-05-12T00:00:00+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://nobita-isc.github.io/blog/2013/05/12/hello-world</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to my new blog, hope you will have a lot of fun here !</p>

<p>Let&rsquo;s get started by introducing myself&hellip;</p>

<p>My name is Vu Xuan Duong, from Vietnam. Currently I am working as a software developer for a software company in Vietnam. I was studying in Japan for 2 years, so I can speak Japanese pretty well. I dont mind if you leave a comment in English, Japanese or Vietnamese.</p>

<p>Currently I want to learn Visual C++ for programming in Windows Enviroment due to job requirement. I am C related language lover but also concern in web programming (both server and client side). I was taking advance in researching about Internet Security in my university. Therefore, it would be glad to see/ share something about security issues in my blog.</p>

<p>Have fun !</p>

<p>nobita-isc</p>

<p>May 12, 2013</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
